<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
    <record id="blogpost3" model="ir.ui.view">
        <field name="name">Blog Post3</field>
        <field name="type">qweb</field>
        <field name="key">smerp_pages.blogpost3</field>
        <field name="arch" type="xml">
            <t name="Blog Post3" t-name="smerp_pages.blogpost3">
                <t t-call="website.layout">
                    <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty blogpost3">
                <main>
    <div class="container-fluid bg-purple">
        <div class="container py-5 text-white">
            <div class="row align-items-center g-4 px-5">
                <div>
                    <div class="pt-3 pb-2 text-center">
                        <h1 class="display-5 fs-2 fw-bold lh-1 mb-3">
                            How to Run a Business with 100% Remote Customers on SMERP Platform<span style="color: #DB0B5B;">.</span>
                        </h1>
                        <p class="">by Admin <small><i>Feb 23, 2022 | 15 MIN</i></small></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="container py-5 px-4">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-12">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-lg-9 mx-auto py-5 mb-4 rounded-3" style="background-color: #FBFBFB;">
                        <div class="row px-5">
                            <div class="col-md-4 mx-auto align-items-center text-center pb-5">
                                <img src="theme_smerp/static/img/smerp-mockup.png" class="img-fluid"
                                alt="..." loading="lazy" height="500" width="500"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-8 mx-auto align-items-center pb-5">
                              <p class="mb-3">
                                <span class="fw-bold fs-2">C</span>onfused? The days of ‘Brick and Mortar’ business are in the past.
                                These days, more and more businesses are popping up daily both on social media platforms
                                (e.g. Instagram, Facebook) or websites. No wonder so many business owners utilize these platforms to
                                their advantage with many shoppers opting to make purchases online rather than walk-in stores.
                                Online purchases and business platforms have been made for your convenience,
                                it is stress-free – pickup or delivery to your doorstep.
                              </p>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-12 justify-content-center">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            Running a business entirely on SMERP  isn’t harder than it looks! With big brands like Konga, Jumia, e.t.c,
                                            leading the way internationally or nationally.
                                            It might seem impossible for smaller businesses to make a splash in this internet boom.
                                            While it might be a little confusing at first, it’s easier than you think to get noticed online.
                                            Keep reading to explore how to run a business with 100% remote customers.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            Nigerian e-commerce platforms have growing competition, there is still a disconnection between businesses
                                            and customers. Customers feel they are interacting with a machine behind the screen.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            Social media buying and selling is also known as a type of online business and it has been in existence for a
                                            long time. Online shopping on social media platforms like Instagram is not without its shortcomings as
                                            shoppers get scammed daily. Such instances of issuance of fake payment alerts, contacting a buyer privately
                                            via WhatsApp without the personal shopper’s consent etc are quite rampant. It’s safer if you know the personal
                                            shopper but what if the person’s account has been hacked. Shopping on Instagram is just luck.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            There are safer platforms like SMERP, which offer a single platform from payment to warehousing.
                                            It’s advisable to transact and manage your business on a secured and protected business platform
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Tips on how to run your business 100%  remotely on SMERP:
                                        <ul>
                                          <li>Keep your navigation simple and easy - A lot of new web designers are tempted to choose designs
                                              that are based more on aesthetics than accessibility.</li>
                                          <li>Cut unnecessary content - Your business content should be clear and precise.</li>
                                          <li>Readability is important - Font sizes should be at least 14 points to be clear and use simple,
                                              un-styled text that is easy to read.</li>
                                          <li>Use strong images - A picture conveys more than a thousand words.
                                              Having strong imagery can keep users on your page longer and it also increases engagement.</li>
                                        </ul>
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        If the above tips are followed, your business will display seamlessly across devices.
                                        Always look for ways to improve your mobile or website optimization.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Making a payment on the ERP platform easily – A customer needs an e-payment system platform that makes it easy for
                                        them to pay securely on the ERP platform. The steps between shopping and entering card information, especially when a
                                        customer abandons their cart and moves onto something else. SMERP makes sure your checkout process is simple and
                                        functional too.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Looking for a payment platform that runs, controls, manages and monetizes your SMEs today?
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        SMERP is the right payment business platform for you and it is essential in running a business smoothly online.
                                        SMERP helps review your account options to ensure you have chosen something secure for your online business.
                                        SMERP provides you with an ERP platform that runs on the cloud and offers SMEs (Retail and Online) the required
                                        tool to manage their entire business operations such as Point of Sale, Inventory and Accounting. Our solution cuts
                                        across all business verticals and aims at reducing the cost of adopting technology as a tool for business growth.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Unfortunately, many small business owners go through a phase of different trials and errors with
                                        several sales and marketing models. Still, the mistake many make is not measuring them to see whether
                                        they are working. Do you want to know a secret to help figure out how well efforts are working, where
                                        to spend the most money, and where to fix it; all you need are Sales metrics to monitor your output and
                                        business as a whole.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Here are 5 business metrics you need to consider while using SMERP; tracking and looking out for your
                                        business performance, growth and  also boost sales:
                                        <ul>
                                          <li>New vs Returning Customers.</li>
                                          <li>Sales Growth Over Time.</li>
                                          <li>Sales By Product or Service.</li>
                                          <li>Sales Generated by Lead Source.</li>
                                          <li>Average Purchase Value.</li>
                                        </ul>
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Thinking of sales metrics as a way to truly connect with your business and its sales operations,
                                        a way to figure out how any decision you make would shape your business’s performance.
                                        The moment your business’s sales monitors are tracked regularly, it becomes easier to prepare a better
                                        plan to revive parts of your sales operations that are lagging in your small business.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            Here are a few things to consider while optimizing your payment system on SMERP
                                          <ul>
                                            <li>Having SMERP A/B test your payment process - the best way to understand which process is the most
                                                effective is to simply test several options.</li>
                                            <li>SMERP reduces unnecessary fees - having a high number of unexpected fees like shipping and handling can lead to more abandoned carts.
                                                Instead, try to offer a flat shipping rate or free shipping for orders over #10,000.</li>
                                            <li>SMERP secures your checkout process - online buyers are hesitant to enter their credit card info in unfamiliar locations.
                                                They need to know their transaction is 100% secure.</li>
                                          </ul>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Unfortunately, many small business owners go through a phase of different trials and errors.
                                        Still, the mistake many make is not measuring them to see whether they are working. Security and ease of
                                        transaction should be your number one priority when your customers are 100% remotely purchasing on the ERP platform.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            SMERP always listens to feedback - Feedback is one of the most valuable resources for any business platform and
                                            you’ll need to pay close attention to customer feedback. Some feedback is digital in the form of analytical information.
                                            How long are users staying on the ERP platform? What business are they visiting, and what are they more interested in?
                                            This feedback is easy to review regularly, and it will help you make the best decisions for your business.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            Encourage users/customers to complete surveys after they purchase items from the ERP platform.
                                            Feedbacks like were they satisfied with their purchase? This kind of feedback shows you how your
                                            business can improve. Need more ways to get genuine customer feedback?
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <hr/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                    </div>

                </div>

            </div>

        </div>



    </div>



</main>




                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </field>
    </record>



    <record id="blogpost3_page" model="website.page">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
        <field name="url">/blogpost3</field>
        <field name="view_id" ref="blogpost3"/>
    </record>

    </data>
</odoo>