<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
    <record id="blogpost2" model="ir.ui.view">
        <field name="name">Blog Post2</field>
        <field name="type">qweb</field>
        <field name="key">smerp_pages.blogpost2</field>
        <field name="arch" type="xml">
            <t name="Blog Post2" t-name="smerp_pages.blogpost2">
                <t t-call="website.layout">
                    <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty blogpost2">
<main>
    <div class="container-fluid bg-purple">
        <div class="container py-5 text-white">
            <div class="row align-items-center g-4 px-5">
                <div>
                    <div class="pt-3 pb-2 text-center">
                        <h1 class="display-5 fs-2 fw-bold lh-1 mb-3">
                            Why Business Management for SMEs is Essential for Growth on SMERP<span style="color: #DB0B5B;">.</span>
                        </h1>
                        <p class="">by Admin <small><i>Feb 22, 2022 | 15 MIN</i></small></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="container py-5 px-4">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-12">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-lg-9 mx-auto py-5 mb-4 rounded-3" style="background-color: #FBFBFB;">
                        <div class="row px-5">
                            <div class="col-md-4 mx-auto align-items-center text-center pb-5">
                                <img src="theme_smerp/static/img/smerp-mockup.png" class="img-fluid"
                                alt="..." loading="lazy" height="500" width="500"/>
                            </div>

                            <div class="col-md-8 mx-auto align-items-center pb-5">
                              <p class="mb-3">
                                <span class="fw-bold fs-2">T</span>hese skills keep your business profitable and thriving for years to come only when you join SMERP.
                              </p>
                              <p class="">
                                Small businesses are essential to the economy. They are job creators, innovators and filled with creators
                                who bring new ideas to market. If you are leading a small business, you know that it’s not easy and there
                                are so many hats you need to wear as a business owner.
                              </p>
                            </div>

                            <div class="col-md-12 justify-content-center">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                            One of the most critical and often overlooked areas in business that you must pay attention to is business management.
                                            But don’t overlook it because good business management skills will keep your business growing and thriving for
                                            years to come. Good business management can be complex for small business owners for various reasons.
                                            Primarily, because business owners started their businesses to tap into the skill they have to offer the world.
                                            They put their effort into the world and earn a living from what they do best, whether selling a product or service.
                                            Chances are you did not take a business class or enough of them to manage a business effectively. And that’s okay.
                                            You can’t be an expert at everything in business.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="fw-bold">
                                            Here are business management tips that can help your business grow on SMERP:
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Here are some of the most commonly faced problems by entrepreneurs when they start to
                                        build their own business;
                                        <ul>
                                          <li class="pb-3">
                                            <b>Create your vision and goals for your business on SMERP</b><br/>
                                            Business management is most effective and efficient when you have a vision and plan that gives you
                                            direction and goals to work towards. Plan out how much revenue you want to earn throughout the year.
                                            Also, plan out the business expenses and your expected profit margins.
                                          </li>

                                          <li class="pb-3">
                                            <b>Manage your business finances</b><br/>
                                            Effective business management includes the cost-effective control of your finances.
                                            As the owner of your business, you do not need to get stuck in the weeds of financial activity.
                                            Still, you need a high-level understanding of your business finances to make profitable decisions for your business.
                                            The purpose of business is to create profit, and the higher the profit margins, the more profit you will have.
                                          </li>

                                          <li class="pb-3">
                                            <b>Set up automation in your business with SMERP</b><br/>
                                            Automation’s platform solutions like SMERP are excellent time-savers and can be cost-effective.
                                            With today’s technology and abundance of time-saving products, you need to take advantage of the technology and set
                                            yourself up for success. Save yourself the stress
                                          </li>

                                          <li class="pb-3">
                                            <b>Listen to your customer’s feedback</b><br/>
                                            Your customers are the drivers of your business, so pay attention when offering you feedback.
                                            Respond to their changing needs and make improvements that they suggest to deliver an excellent customer experience.
                                            Happy customers spread the word and bring in new business.
                                          </li>

                                          <li class="pb-3">
                                            <b>Listen to your team</b><br/>
                                            Visionary small business owners should hire intelligent people.
                                            You do a disservice to the business when you are not listening and implementing your team’s feedback and suggestions.
                                            Don’t surround yourself with yes people; surround yourself with people who have new ideas that are not afraid to express them.
                                            New and innovative thinking helps the business grow.
                                          </li>

                                          <li class="pb-3">
                                            <b>Build good relationships</b><br/>
                                            Business is enjoyable, especially when we keep the human element as part of the business.
                                            You can have the most intelligent person on your team, but if they kill your team's morale,
                                            the business will suffer. Build good relationships with your customers.
                                          </li>

                                          <li>
                                            <b>Be resilient on SMERP</b><br/>
                                            Resilience is critical in business, as market demand changes rapidly and what worked today may no
                                            longer work tomorrow. It would be best to flow with the changes and alter your plan accordingly to
                                            survive. <br/><br/>
                                            The bottom line is that there are so many areas in your business that need attention to flow together successfully.
                                            Yes, generating revenue is a vital component of a business.
                                            But, don’t forget about the backend office activities that require attention.
                                            Every action in your business affects the bottom line, whether it’s directly or indirectly.
                                            Be sure you have tightened up your backend services to ensure you are meeting the highest profit potential in
                                            your business
                                          </li>
                                        </ul>
                                      </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <hr/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>

        </div>



    </div>

</main>




                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </field>
    </record>



    <record id="blogpost2_page" model="website.page">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
        <field name="url">/blogpost2</field>
        <field name="view_id" ref="blogpost2"/>
    </record>

    </data>
</odoo>