<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="blogpost1" model="ir.ui.view">
        <field name="name">Blog Post1</field>
        <field name="type">qweb</field>
        <field name="key">smerp_pages.blogpost1</field>
        <field name="arch" type="xml">
            <t name="Blog Post1" t-name="smerp_pages.blogpost1">
                <t t-call="website.layout">
                    <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty blogpost1">
<main>
    <div class="container-fluid bg-purple">
        <div class="container py-5 text-white">
            <div class="row align-items-center g-4 px-5">
                <div>
                    <div class="pt-3 pb-2 text-center">
                        <h1 class="display-5 fs-2 fw-bold lh-1 mb-3">
                          Think you’re too old to be an entrepreneur? Think Again<span style="color: #DB0B5B;">.</span>
                        </h1>
                        <p class="">by Admin <small><i>Feb 21, 2022 | 10 MIN</i></small></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="container py-5 px-4">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-12">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-lg-9 mx-auto py-5 mb-4 rounded-3" style="background-color: #FBFBFB;">
                        <div class="row px-5">
                            <div class="col-md-4 mx-auto align-items-center text-center pb-5">
                                <img src="theme_smerp/static/img/smerp-mockup.png" class="img-fluid"
                                alt="..." loading="lazy" height="500" width="500"/>
                            </div>

                            <div class="col-md-8 mx-auto align-items-center pb-5">
                              <p class="mb-3">
                                <span class="fw-bold fs-2">A</span>re you an entrepreneur? Are you thinking of starting your business?
                                Are you looking for a business platform? If your answer is yes, join SMERP today and do all
                                your business transactions on a single ERP platform seamlessly.
                              </p>

                              <p class="">
                                An entrepreneur is an individual who focuses on creating new businesses and companies.
                                An entrepreneur and SMEs bear all the risks in starting a new business and they are commonly seen
                                as a motivator and an innovator.
                              </p>
                            </div>

                            <div class="col-md-12 justify-content-center">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                          Entrepreneurs play a significant role in maintaining the economy of a country.
                                          They should continuously develop new ideas, implement them, and finally release them to the market.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                        <span class="">
                                          Even though an entrepreneur bears all the risks, those who succeed in taking all the risks
                                          head-on and overcome them are treated with immense profit, fame, other unique ideas,
                                          and business opportunities from other investors.
                                        </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Here are some of the most commonly faced problems by entrepreneurs when they start to
                                        build their own business;
                                        <ul>
                                          <li>Overcoming the norms and bureaucracy.</li>
                                          <li>Hiring people.</li>
                                          <li>Obtaining funding and financing.</li>
                                        </ul>
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Is Age a Factor to be an entrepreneur?
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        We know that being an entrepreneur implies that the person should face risks and problems head-on.
                                        By successful entrepreneurs, we generally think of people such as Jeff Bezos, Bill Gates, Mark Zuckerberg, Steve Jobs,
                                         etc. All these famous entrepreneurs started their own company when they were just 20 years old.
                                         So, does that imply that only young people can choose entrepreneurship as their career?
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        So, how old are you? Do you think it’s too late to possibly quit your current job and start a new business or a company?
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        If you think being 40 years old can destroy your possible career as an entrepreneur,
                                        you are entirely wrong. Age doesn’t matter in starting your own business.
                                        If you believe you can start your own business, then it is the only thing required to attain success.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        When you look at successful companies or businesses, you can see that the average age of a founder or owner goes up, not down.
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Now, one of the advantages of starting your company or business late are:
                                        <ul>
                                          <li>Greater access to financial resources. For example, you can invest in your company from your pocket and not depend on others.</li>
                                          <li>You will have a ton of experience from your previous company. This might be extremely helpful when you start your own company or business.</li>
                                          <li>As you would have a lot of experience, you would have built a vast network that might be useful.</li>
                                        </ul>
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        Now, why do people view entrepreneurs as very young people?
                                      </span>
                                    </div>

                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-3">
                                      <span class="">
                                        It is because people’s mindset is fixated such that people only look for retirement after 40 years
                                        and work to save money for the future. And at 65, we see ourselves as ready to retire.
                                        It’s not too late to start a business or company of your own. If you don’t try, then how do you make it?
                                      </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <hr/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>

    </div>

</main>



                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </field>
    </record>



    <record id="blogpost1_page" model="website.page">
        <field name="website_published">True</field>
        <field name="url">/blogpost1</field>
        <field name="view_id" ref="blogpost1"/>
    </record>


    </data>
</odoo>